<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <currentVersion>1.2.3100</currentVersion>
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <description>
[anchor]MiddleCenter[/anchor][b]Vehicles - 1.2.3100[/b][anchor]MiddleLeft[/anchor]
[title]Notes[/title][font]Tiny[/font]
Hey everyone, another update for the framework is out! This update brings along many bugfixes to turrets and shuttle mechanics as well as new additions regarding air defenses and turret animation.

A new save game is recommended for this update.
[title]Bug Fixes[/title][font]Tiny[/font]
Fixed bug where WorldObjects in a loaded game would not reregister valid air defenses.

Fixed bug where aerial vehicle would be pushed to circle destination due to landing altitude being slightly under mark.

Fixed bug where strafe run would not allow targeting.

Fixed bug where TurretTop_Recoiled would only tick recoil when manned.

Fixed bug where VehicleTurrets would not fire with godMode enabled.

Fixed bug where VehicleTurret would not auto-reload after running out of ammo.

Fixed bug where choosing new FlightPath would re-randomize the angle of active AirDefense search lights.

Fixed bug where AerialVehicles would not take damage from air defense projectiles.
[title]New Additions[/title]
Changed the way Settlement Air Defenses are cached.

Air Defenses can now be attached to any world objects as a WorldComp.

Added VerbProperties_Recoil, Verb_ShootRecoiled, Building_RecoiledTurret, and TurretTop_Recoiled classes for recoil animation.

Added 88mm Flak 36 artillery for Flak type air defense.
[gif delay=40 height=400 fps=20]FlakDemo[/gif]
Added new verb for recoiled turrets.

Added spotlight targeters for air defenses.

Added dragging for patterns. Allows the player to move the pattern applied to the vehicle for desired effect.
[title]Additional Changes[/title]
Cleaned up AntiAircraft world objects for more field settings.

Flak now fire from an offset and in intervals.

Air Defenses can now be generated for WorldObjects with varying amounts and with specific anti aircraft defs.

AntiAircraftDef now defines both a minimum and maximum striking altitude.

UI clean up in Dialog_ColorPicker.

Changed how updates are cached. Previous version updates may now be accessed in the DevMode tab in the Mod Settings.

Crash Landings will now trigger when the altitude meter hits 0 and the descent is uncontrolled.  Running out of fuel and losing flight control will both result in an uncontrollable descent. You may now glide to try to get closer to an easier to rescue tile.
[title]Final Notes[/title]
Please report any issues you find [link]https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/issues[/link](here.)
  </description>
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <update>true</update>
  <testing>true</testing>
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon.png</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon.png</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon.png</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Support Vehicles Development</name>
      <icon>ko-fiIcon.png</icon>
      <url>https://ko-fi.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>