<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.5.1356</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
This update comes with some critical bugfixes to pathfinding and regions.  Your vehicles shouldn't have any problems going through garages, and they definitely won't be pathfinding over walls anymore.

Next update will be focusing on everything related to Vehicle Caravans.  I understand they're not perfect right now, so next update should alleviate that.
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed bug where vehicles weren't triggering path recalculation when moving

- Fixed bug where path grids were only updating for vehicle region owners, allowing some vehicles to path over walls.

- Fixed bug where even-width vehicles (eg. 2x4) would get stuck when stopped near a wall.

- Fixed thread safety issues related to pulling thing lists during region recaching and pathfinding.

- Fixed bug where defining a vehicle turret without a shaderType would throw an exception on startup.

- Fixed bug where path grids wouldn't update when setting terrain via devmode.

- Fixed bug where vehicle caravans wouldn't render fuel gizmos for multiple vehicles in a caravan.

- Fixed bug where loading an older save with a vehicle on the world map (with turrets) would throw an exception upon returning.
&lt;title&gt;Performance Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Async actions are now pooled

- ThingList snapshots are now pooled
&lt;title&gt;Compatibility Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Roads of the Rim

- Dynamic Trade interface
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Added default 'Vehicles' tab for modders.  Use this instead of creating a dozen different designation categories.

- Changed even-width vehicles from rounding up for region padding. 2xN vehicles can now fit through 2-cell gaps, rather than requiring 3.

- DamageDefs that aren't meant to harm health no longer damage vehicles (EMP, Smoke, Extinguish, etc.)
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find on the &lt;link&gt;https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ&lt;/link&gt;(discord server).</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>