<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.3.8165</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Recent News&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Hey everyone, another weekly update with tons of changes.  The current pace I've been working at is a huge time commitment, so let's keep it going while there are bugs to report!

&lt;b&gt;This update I am very confident that Vehicle Caravans are in working condition&lt;/b&gt;.  So PLEASE test very thoroughly.
I'm adding balance changes each update so it's a bit more convenient to use in actual games.

Again, I don't care how minor the bug or feedback is, everything helps. Thanks again!
&lt;title&gt;Balance Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Rowboat (Buildable)&lt;/b&gt;
- Reduced MaxHitPoints from 10000 to 50
- Increased WorkToBuild from 30 to 200
- Changed costList from 1 ComponentIndustrial to 35 WoodLog
- Increased Flammability from 0.05 to 0.65
&lt;b&gt;Rowboat (Vehicle)&lt;/b&gt;
- Decreased CargoCapacity from 300 to 75
- Decreased MarketValue from 250000 to 85
- Increased Flammability from 0 to 0.65
- Decreased Mass from 10000 to 35

&lt;b&gt;Fishing Boat (Buildable)&lt;/b&gt;
- Reduced MaxHitPoints from 10000 to 250
- Increased WorkToBuild from 30 to 1500
- Changed costList from 35 ComponentIndustrial and 3000 Steel to 140 WoodLog
- Increased Flammability from 0.05 to 0.65
&lt;b&gt;Fishing Boat (Vehicle)&lt;/b&gt;
- Decreased MarketValue from 250000 to 250
- Increased Flammability from 0 to 0.65
- Decreased Mass from 10000 to 200

&lt;b&gt;Sparrow (Buildable)&lt;/b&gt;
- Reduced MaxHitPoints from 5000 to 750
- Increased WorkToBuild from 30 to 85000
- Changed costList from 35 ComponentIndustrial and 3000 Steel to 12 ComponentSpacer, 500 Steel, and 250 Plasteel
&lt;b&gt;Sparrow (Vehicle)&lt;/b&gt;
- Decreased MarketValue from 250000 to 175000
- Decreased Mass from 25000 to 6200
- Removed VehicleTurrets, they were for testing only and the main focus for now will just be normal flying (not strafing or bombing runs)
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed bug where GenSteps would attempt to recalculate vehicle path cost when regions had not been built yet. (Fixes compatibility with Biomes Core mods)

- Fixed bug where arriving skyfallers would attempt to notify VehicleTracks comp a tick after its removal.

- Fixed bug with shaders where the color math would result in artifacting at the borders of the color channels.

- Fixed bug where VehiclePawn would occasionally spawn inside stone chunks in an event map.

- Fixed bug where AerialVehicle could be selected to drop out of bounds, resulting in the loss of the vehicle and its crew.

- Fixed bug where auto-targeting VehicleTurrets' targeter would still be active even after vehicle has been despawned.

- Fixed event map VehicleCaravan reformations

- Fixed bug where settlement maps wouldn't take pawns inside vehicles into account when calculating points.

- Fixed bug where selecting multiple pawns (with at least one of them actively reserving a vehicle) and then right clicking it would throw a reservation exception.

- Fixed bug where VehicleRequestCollection wasn't saving
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
- Removed irrelevant ResearchProjectDefs

- Performance improvements to VehicleTurrets.

- Split Patterns and Skins to separate shaders to remove all branching logic from shader files.

- Added 2 ResearchProjectDefs for Rowboat and FishingBoat. More will follow later when the mod is closer to releasing.

- Added SkinDefs back into the mod for testing

- Improved VTOL animation of Sparrow

- Changed vertical ticks to instead be a property of individual launch or land properties, allowing you to designate different tick counts for landing and launching vertical animations.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find &lt;link&gt;https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/issues&lt;/link&gt;(here.) or on the discord server.
</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>