<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.4.1331</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Recent News&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
I've created a community managed google spreadsheet for translations, so if you want to help fill out one of the languages please DM me on discord and I can add you. Feel free to join even if the language you know is already filled out, I may need to edit or add entries in the future.  Thanks! :)
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed bug where vehicles at corner of maps can clip out of bounds and be deleted.

- Fixed bug where rotating while targeting landing would change the rotation of the vehicle actively.

- Fixed bug where vehicle would pull incorrect landing properties while targeting.

- Fixed bug where patterns would copy from incorrect rotation for material generation.

- Fixed bug where aerial vehicles were unable to offer gifts.

- Fixed bug where pawns would not transfer to inventory upon death inside vehicles.

- Fixed bug with turret recaching status not triggering on pawn death.

- Compatibility fix for TraderGen.

- Compatibility fix for RimHUD.

- Fixed bug where turrets would rotate incorrectly in UI at UIScale &gt; 1.

- Fixed bug where reserving handlers would get cleared immediately, allowing multiple pawns to enter the same role beyond the limit.

- Fixed bug where aerial vehicles would ignore situations that should prevent the vehicle from launching on the world map.

- Fixed bug where loading save file that saved while turret was shooting throws an exception, causing the vehicle to not load in.

- Fixed bug where vehicles could still be drafted with out of fuel.
&lt;title&gt;Performance Improvements&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Added additional configuration options for runway restrictions.

- Changed default color palettes.

- Added toggle for patterns and skins displayed.

- Added &gt;M options for loading cargo into vehicles.

- Default auto-refuel percentage changed from 30% to 100%, meaning all vehicles will request to be refueled to full capacity if they are currently undrafted.

- Added extra info when trading with AerialVehicle at settlement.

- Cleaned up all translation files and added spreadsheet for tracking all translations.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find &lt;link&gt;https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ&lt;/link&gt;(discord server).</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>