<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.5.1422</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>GameInit</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Hey everyone, this update comes with a lot of fixes for caravans and aerial vehicles on the world map.  

Please give the list of bugs a read, I know it's super long but previously unusable mechanics are now fixed and I'd hate for anyone to miss out. For example, pathfinding should now be fixed as well as janky caravan formations or entering maps stacked on top of each other.

I'm slowly inching closer towards having Vehicle Framework free of critical bugs, which means I can start on raiders / traders soon (within the next few patches).  Yay!  If you guys have feedback or ideas you'd like to pitch for raiders / traders, lemme know.  I'll be designing the mechanics soon.

Here's a sneak peek of something I'm working on: &lt;gif WIDTH=300 SIZE=(13,13) FPS=30 &gt;ParatrooperRaid.gif&lt;/gif&gt;
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed pathfinding bug where neighboring regions were not updated properly, causing areas to be unreachable.

- Aerial Vehicles transition to caravans when landed, allowing sites / quests to be interacted with properly.

- Fixed bug where launching 2 aerial vehicles to land in the same map at the same time would fail to start targeting for the 2nd aerial vehicle.

- Fixed bug where downed pawns were unable to be set for loading in any UI, including vanilla transport pods, caravans, and even reformation dialogs.

- Fixed bug where merging any vehicle caravan would not recache the colonist bar.

- Fixed bug where ordering aerial vehicle to fly to the same tile it launched from causes game to crash.

- Fixed bug where any caravan merging with vehicles would not guarantee that it spawns a vehicle caravan, missing out on the custom pathfinding among other mechanics.

- Fixed bug where loading a save would cause vehicle caravans to not resume their saved path.

- Fixed bug where entering a map with more than 1 vehicle caused vehicles to stack, making them hard to move (if not downright impossibly stuck).

- Fixed bug where pawns in vehicle caravan would rest 24/7.

- Fixed bug where loading cargo into a vehicle would sometimes issue too many jobs, or try to issue multiple jobs on the same item.

- Fixed bug where pawns inside vehicles would not try to recover psyfocus and hemogen.

- Fixed bug where Load Pawn gizmo would not properly mark downed colonists for loading.

- Fixed bug where colonists would refuel vehicle while it's leaking, resulting in wasted fuel.

- Fixed bug where targeting for launching aerial vehicles would throw an exception for any vehicles without a fuel component.

- Fixed bug where AerialVehicle world map icon would rotate 90 degrees when zoomed in.

- Fixed bug where the aim pie of vehicle turrets would flicker when rendering.

- Fixed bug where vehicle turrets with infinite range wouldn't be affected by spread radius.

- Fixed bug where vehicle turrets with generic ammo wouldn't be able to ignore LOS for targeting with overhead projectiles.

&lt;title&gt;Compatibility Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Geological Landforms

- Real Ruins
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Removed "Dock Boat" option from vehicle caravans.  It was buggy and it has since been re-implemented as an all-purpose "stash vehicles" button to go on foot and leave vehicles behind for up to 20-30 days.  It will show when your caravan is stopped.

- Added pawn rendering to TweakField menu, allowing runtime editing of pawn rendering fields.

- Increased brightness of text in Cargo tab for items yet to be loaded.

- Added damage field to explosive vehicle parts, allowing overriding of damage applied.

- Rebalanced painting vehicles to take less time and not scale as drastically with larger vehicles.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find on the &lt;link&gt;https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ&lt;/link&gt;(discord server).</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name.-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name.-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
  <!--Images to download off the web to reference from the description.-->
  <images>
    <li>
      <name>ParatrooperRaid.gif</name>
      <url>https://i.imgur.com/AOSeSdX.jpg</url>
    </li>
  </images>
</UpdateLog>