<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.5.1338</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Hey everyone! Hope you're enjoying the mod so far, I've gotten a lot of feedback which is great. Things aren't utterly breaking, even in bigger mod lists, so I'm confident with a bit more work I can get this running smoothly for the majority of mod packs.

I am aware of an inconsistent bug where regions aren't recaching, causing vehicles to be unable to enter / exit some areas. I'm still trying to pinpoint what exactly causes it, as it's an edge case and very hard to reproduce for me for some reason.  In the mean time, reloading your game will resolve the issue.  Same goes for some maps not being able to form caravans for vehicles, I'm looking into it!

That's all I've got for now, I'll push another patch soon-ish once I've made some more fixes.  Thanks again for all the support and feedback! You guys are awesome.
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed bug where vehicles could be drafted if fueled but unmanned, but were still unable to move.

- Fixed compatibility issue with Prepare Carefully when spawning with vehicles in the presets.

- Fixed bug where project build date wouldn't get parsed correctly for Mac and Linux users.

- Fixed bug where large numbers of vehicles would not properly scroll in the vehicle list of the mod settings.

- Fixed bug where firefoam poppers and mortar shells would deal 999,999 damage to vehicles.

- Fixed compatibility issue with Carry Capacity Fixed.

- Fixed bug where hovering over stats in the info page throws an exception.

- Fixed bug where pawns would be unable to load items into vehicles during caravan formation.

- Fixed bug where vehicle health labels weren't updating properly.

- Fixed bug where VehicleCaravans would save duplicate entries in vehicle and WorldPawns, causing issues on loading.

- Fixed bug where tutor system would trigger when forming vehicle caravan, causing the tutorial window to open permanently for some people until the game was reloaded.

- Fixed bug where space-faring vehicles traveling to RimNauts locations would travel to the location from launch, rather than the updated DrawPos.
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Added Spanish translation

- Added Portuguese (Brazilian) translation

- Fixed translation folder names

- Moved compatibility over from RimNauts to RimNauts 2 (requested by RimNauts devs)

- Added thread check for path follower

- Added option to refuel vehicles from inventory, including in caravans.  A pawn must be inside and if it's an aerial vehicle it cannot be in the air (eg. must be stationary if on the world map)

- All DevMode gizmos are now locked behind godMode setting.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find on the &lt;link&gt;https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ&lt;/link&gt;(discord server).</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>