<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.3.8295</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Recent News&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
The mod is officially released for testing. Visit the discord server for more information.
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed issue with DynamicDrawnWorldObjects on the world map where the mod setting wasn't properly applied

- Fixed bug where air defenses were still drawing their perimeter radius despite being disabled.

- Fixed compatibility issue with XmlExtensions, which would cause a fatal error and CTD.

- Fixed bug where changing a vehicle's movement permissions would not update cached moveable defs, requiring a restart.

- Fixed bug where vehicle's info card would throw exception upon closing.

- Fixed CTD compatibility issue with XmlExtensions and Hugslib.

- Fixed bug where CutoutComplex and Cutout would not properly apply vanilla mask with vehicles.

- Fixed bug where damaging a vehicle would trigger the DraftOn/DraftOff events.

- Fixed bug where pawn would go to (0, 0) on the map while repairing vehicle.

- Fixed bug where pawn would go to (0, 0) when given a prioritized vehicle job.

- Fixed bug where vehicle pathgrid would not update when some Things were destroyed.

- Fixed bug where vehicle turrets would take too much ammo or not refund enough ammo when configured w/ chargePerAmmoCount.

- Fixed bug where vehicle pathing costs were not properly calculated, resulting in zig zags when pathing behind the vehicle.

- Fixed bug where vehicle caravans would calculate incorrect movement ticks.

- Fixed duplicate float menu option bug for repair / paint.
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
- Modified chance of instant death when boat sinks over deep water

- Added Drowning hediff that applies to pawns in sinking ship (proportional to manipulation / movement capacities average)

- Added pawn rendering + icon for disembarking individual pawns from a vehicle

- Added VehicleTurret restriction mechanics, allowing for turret to be enabled or disabled only if certain conditions are met (eg. must be stationary to aim + shoot)

- Added Reactor mechanics to VehicleComponents.  Reactors are event based mechanics that will trigger certain mechanics when a vehicle component takes damage. (eg. explode, leak fuel, etc.)

- Gizmos for unloading pawns inside the vehicle now render the pawn instead of a generic icon

- Painting a vehicle now requires a pawn to perform the paint job on the vehicle, rather than being instantaneous

- Vehicles can be given a deconstruct designator, breaking the vehicle apart into a fraction of its cost.

- Added basic information to vehicle info card

- Reworked job limitations to apply to prioritized jobs rather than just workgivers.

- Added vehicle stat parts that can be applied to specific vehicle defs and not just entire vehicle stat defs.

- Adjusted ModSettings UI for better float and integer box inputs.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find &lt;link&gt;https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/issues&lt;/link&gt;(here.) or on the discord server.
</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>