<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.5.1701</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>GameInit</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
This update includes many Quality of Life features such as designating roads, reorienting aerial vehicles upon landing, reorienting vehicles upon pathing to a destination, and more.

Be sure to take a look at the full list down below, and as always if you have feedback feel free to drop by the discord. Thanks!

Note: This version is a hotfix of 1.5.1700, fixing the issue where Camera+'s and Mark That Pawn's patch on vehicle rendering broke. 
If you removed either during the wait, you can now safely re-add them.
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Upgrading FuelCapacity wouldn't update amount needed to refuel, causing pawns to attempt to refuel in a loop.

- Under specific circumstances a vehicle would become 'incapacitated'

- Overlays would attempt to initialize outside of the main thread when loading a save.

- Vehicle role removal upgrade refunding would add the role copied from the upgrade, rather than checking if it was originally from the vehicle def.

- Compatibility patch for Rails and Roads of the Rim

- AsyncRegionRegisterAction exception when loading a map, causing some regions to become malformed in the process.

- Concurrency issue when updating regions, resulting in invalid regions marked for dirtying not having their cells persist in the dirty set.

- Vehicle leaks would not reset their status when repaired once the fuel count had reached 0.

- CompUpgradeTree attempting to validate listers even if the vehicle is unspawned but being ticked elsewhere (such as in Save Our Ship 2 when traveling between ships).
&lt;title&gt;Performance Optimization&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Parallelized Vehicle Region generation when loading a map.
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Players&lt;/b&gt;
- Added Road zone to direct vehicles over paths, and to note which edges to try and exit from for caravans.

- Items dropped from cargo will be placed outside of the vehicle's hitbox.

- Vehicles can drag-to-rotate by holding right click when ordering to go to a location. This will rotate the vehicle to face this rotation after arriving at the destination.

- Aerial vehicles with forced rotations for animations can now be rotated during landing, which will rotate the vehicle to face this rotation after it has landed.

- Upgrades will refund % of cost if upgrade is reset or vehicle is deconstructed / destroyed.

- Only explosive mortar shells will have their explosion radius reduced when impacting water, as opposed to every shell.

- VehicleTurret aim pies hidden if vehicle is not selected.
&lt;b&gt;Modders&lt;/b&gt;
- Added CompUpgrade for adding / removing comps from upgrades
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find on either &lt;link&gt;https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ&lt;/link&gt;(discord) or &lt;link&gt;https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicle-Framework/issues&lt;/link&gt;(github).</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name.-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3014915404</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name.-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>