<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.3.8142</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Recent News&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Hey everyone, it's time for some major testing. With caravans and their formations working, we are now in the testing phase.

If you aren't already, please join the discord! If you're in the VE testing server, that works too. Once the remaining bugs are stomped out, I'll be prepping it for a steam release.

It's very important that all major bugs are found, because once the mod releases, I'm going to have to deal with not breaking save games in subsequent updates.

Thanks again for sticking around for over 2 years of development!
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Fixed bug where vehicle caravans did not properly display the vehicles in it.

Fixed bug where VehicleTurret would rotate 90 degrees upon loading a game.

Fixed bug where caravan formation for Vehicles would break on gather items.

Fixed bug where caravans would mistakenly assign an exit point that was unreachable for vehicles

Fixed display issue with caravans not showing details for vehicles or items within them

Fixed bug where UI would break from an exception when no vehicles were selected.

Fixed bug where formation LordJob would not contain any land vehicles.

Fixed bug where assigned seating of caravan formation would not update.

Fixed bug with giving items to a vehicle would throw an exception.

Fixed bug where settling in a map with a vehicle would boot you back to main menu.

Fixed bug where you could not trade with settlements.

Fixed bug where boats would path over bridges.

Fixed bug where vehicle caravans were unable to form on non-colony maps.

Fixed bug where pawns with disabled stat for trading would trigger an error in StatWorker for attempting to calculate a disabled stat.

Fixed bug where adding a vehicle in the dialog window would not dirty caravan max capacity.

Fixed bug where FormCaravan dialog of vehicles would throw exception when choosing a route with pawns but no vehicles.

Fixed bug where removing vehicle from caravan dialog would not update assigned seating.

Fixed bug where you could remove pawns from caravan dialog but leave them assigned to vehicles.  Pawns will now be readonly if assigned to a vehicle in caravan formation dialog. Removing the vehicle from the caravan dialog will remove all assigned pawns as well.

Fixed bug where removing and readding a vehicle that was recently given changed seating would revert to old seating assignments.
&lt;title&gt;New Additions&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Float menu option added for shuttles and trading with friendly settlements.

Vehicles can now exit event maps if there is an exit border.

&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
-
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find &lt;link&gt;https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/issues&lt;/link&gt;(here.) or on the discord server.
</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>