<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.4.1225</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Recent News&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
Tons of bugfixes! If you are currently in the middle of a game, make sure you revert back to 1.4.1079 as this version will require a new game.
&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Fixed compatibility issue with Vanilla Expanded Psycasts.

- Fixed bug where forcing a vehicle into a mental state or mental break would bypass its previous preventative measures.

- Fixed bug where forcing a hediff onto a vehicle would immediately destroy it.

- Fixed bug where aerial vehicles wouldn't use fuel under certain conditions.

- Fixed some grammar issues for jobs labels for pawns.

- Fixed bug where vehicles would attempt to pull dropdown for school mechanics.

- Fixed bug where pawns weren't ticking inside the vehicle that was spawned on a map, causing them to enter a suspended state.

- Fixed bug where using StackLimit mods would cause adding ammo to vehicle turrets via devmode to add hundreds or thousands at a time, overencumbering the vehicle.

- Fixed bug where creating a vehicle turret that did not require ammo to reload was impossible.

- Fixed bug where vehicle reservations and requesters wouldn't properly clear when vehicle is despawned.

- Fixed bug where canceling loading while pawns are actively hauling still attempts to load the items anyway.

- Fixed bug where default terrain would not be marked impassable but still invalid for pathfinding, resulting in floodfill searches due to reachability checks not working.

- Fixed compatibility issue with Vanilla Psycasts Expanded.

- Fixed bug where vehicles would tick comps on world map.

- Fixed bug where jobs would display duplicate float menu for repairing and painting.

- Fixed visual issues where caravan speed, food left, and mass usage were not accurate to the vehicles in the caravan.

- Fixed bug where vehicle turret rotation would reset upon loading a save.

- Fixed PawnPathPool memory leak when queueing multiple paths for a vehicle.

- Fixed visual bug with vehicle icons not masking inside scroll rects.

- Fixed bug with RoutePlanner selections rendering off screen.

- Fixed bug where resetting a vehicle in the ModSettings wouldn't reset the pattern data.

- Fixed bug where vehicle turrets not using a mask would render transparent in gizmos.

- Fixed bug where gizmos would size incorrectly according to enabled features.

- Fixed issue where vehicle turret would persist in the turret queue if an exception was thrown, rendering the turret unusable.

- Fixed bug where attached turrets would adjust incorrectly to the parent.

- Fixed graphic overlay offsets not adjusting correctly for icons.

- Fixed issue where projectile flags would override the def.

- Fixed bug where vehicle would still attempt to path into impassable cells.

- Fixed bug where vehicles spawning would not execute the Spawn event on loaded games.

- Fixed bug where CompFueledTravel was unable to tick on the world map.

- Fixed bug with AerialVehicles not loading correctly from a save file while in flight, causing them to be unusable unless landed through devmode.

- Fixed visual issues with caravan gizmo for dismounted pawns, foraging of dismounted pawns, and visibility.

- Fixed bug where AssignDefaults xml attribute would execute prematurely, incorrectly loading xml data.

- Fixed bug with extended pathfinding while validating the min hitbox rect, causing CTD.

- Fixed bug where a vehicle pathing near the edge of a map could clip off map, causing it to be destroyed.

- Fixed bug where pawns would not be able to board the vehicle due to an improper last minute validation check of the handler.

- Fixed bug where pawns were not able to be tended to while inside the vehicle.

- Fixed bug where FormCaravan lord job of vehicles did not save correctly.

- Fixed bug where vehicles would exit map prematurely next to edge of map due to increased distance check.

- Fixed bug where canceling a caravan with pawns already boarded would not clear the duties of the pawns onboard.

- Fixed issue with multi vehicle caravans not being able to properly path to the exit point.

- Fixed bug where trading with an animal in the caravan would throw an exception.

- Fixed bug where traders would not pick up player inventory when caravan was sent instantly through devmode.

- Fixed bug where vehicles that ran out of fuel on the world map would still be able to function.

- Fixed compatibility issue with Roads of the Rim.

- Fixed visual bug with wound overlays rendering over vehicles despite the vehicle being over the building / pawn.
&lt;title&gt;Performance Improvements&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Compressed region making for vehicles to reuse region grids for vehicles with similar configurations.

- Calculations for vehicles' world path grid are now thrown into a separate thread.  This will prevent the game from locking up once per in-game-day when it recalculates for seasonal costs.

- Vehicle comps will now only tick on request, rather than every comp ticking continuously despite not being in use.

- Improved startup time substantially.  This is especially apparent for large mod lists, startup time should be relatively consistent now regardless of mod list size.

- Vehicle stats are now cached and calculated only when needed.  Event driven recaching will also allow unused stats to remain uncalculated until fetched. (Schrödinger's stat)

- Removed unnecessary tickers from VehiclePawn.

- Regions are now managed, dirtyed, and updated on the dedicated map thread for vehicles.

- HPA* implementation for faster cross-map pathfinding.

- Pathfinding is now performed on the dedicated map thread for vehicles.

- Fixed some old patches for detecting pawns inside vehicles for events such as Game Ender and alerts.

- DefDatabase changes for better memory allocation.

- VehicleTurret role caching for better validation when firing.
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
- Changed FuelConsumptionCondition to operate on flags.  Defaults to consuming fuel when drafted or moving in a caravan.

- Added configuration button for target fuel level of vehicle.

- Added indicator to target fuel level of vehicle.

- Added gizmo of Fuel Count for vehicles on world map.

- Vehicles are no longer able to be refueled while drafted.

- Vehicles stop dead when clicking 'undraft' gizmo while moving, rather than undrafting immediately.

- Added vehicle turret events.

- Added high path costs for vehicles, giving high avoidal to paths found with vehicles in the search radius.

- Vehicles stop dead before overlapping other vehicle while pathing. 2 Vehicles pathing into each other will trigger a 'stop and wait' or search for a new path.

- Added WITabs for vehicle caravans that display all pawns (including vehicles) in the caravan.

- Added seat swapping for caravans, allowing pawns to be moved around or even disembarked from a vehicle.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find &lt;link&gt;https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ&lt;/link&gt;(discord server).</description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>true</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Cursed Crew</name>
      <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
    </li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>