<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<UpdateLog>
  <!--Can utilize Version.txt file placed in mod's root directory-->
  <currentVersion>1.3.7902</currentVersion>
  <!--Startup,GameInit,LoadedGame,NewGame-->
  <updateOn>Startup</updateOn>
  <!--Full description shown in update page-->
  <description>&lt;title&gt;Recent News&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Small&lt;/font&gt;
I've started a &lt;link&gt;https://www.patreon.com/smashphil&lt;/link&gt;(Patreon) for Vehicles development if you're interested in supporting further development of the mod.
&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;&lt;title&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/title&gt;
Fixed compatibility issue with Nature's Pretty Sweet, despawning objects immediately after spawning on lava while still triggering VehicleRegions to generate.

Fixed bug where AerialVehicles on the world map would still render with lighting when zoomed out.

Fixed bug where AirDefenses would not serialize properly resulting in Load issues.

Fixed bug where other materials would not render on top of materials using ShaderRGB or ShaderRGBPattern, causing obfuscation of the other material.

Fixed bug where VTOLTakeoff would not properly tick the vertical animation, resulting in only the main landing sequence animating.

Fixed bug where launch protocols for landing animations would instead set to maxTicks of launchProperties.

Fixed bug where overlays wouldn't take layering into account.

Fixed bug where forced takeoff rotation wouldn't execute for specific cell arrivals.

Fixed bug where Smashtools settings for unit testing would save specific to the mod it was included in. This was caused by the behavior of vanilla mod settings and should be fine now in regards to this tool being used in other mods.

Fixed bug where main turret would not load proper graphic data under specific circumstances.
&lt;title&gt;New Additions&lt;/title&gt;
Added ExtraRotationRegistry class which handles extra rotation for overlays.

Added Graphic_Rotator class to register extra rotation key in the ExtraRotationRegistry for any graphic class inheriting Graphic_Rotator.

Added PropellerTakeoff launch protocol for a VTOL based takeoff where the propellers first wind up.

Reimplemented GraphicDataLayered to work as an easy to implement data class to convert whole number layers into evenly layered offsets without jumping into other AltitudeLayers. This should be the goto method for layering graphics (both for VehicleTurrets and GraphicOverlays, DO NOT TRY TO FORCE IT THROUGH DRAW OFFSET)

Default pattern of vehicle is now split up into default GraphicDataRGB, meaning you can change the default pattern, color, colorTwo, colorThree, displacement, and tiles.  These default settings will apply ingame like the default pattern did.

Added 2 more variations of the main turret for the Tank. I had the extra textures due to the previous way the turret was animated so I figured I'd put them to use :) if it feels out of place let me know.
&lt;title&gt;Additional Changes&lt;/title&gt;
Changed the UpdateLog to now allow multiple mods to throw update notifications, allowing the user to page through all updates. I'll release this modder tool at a later time for other modders.

Added rotation SimpleCurves for VTOLTakeoff to handle rotation of the vehicle while it is being vertically lifted before switching to using the launch or landing rotation simple curve.

Lowered OpenGL build to allow better support of the custom pattern shaders for lower end GPUs. This should fix the issues on Linux as well but please report that if any of you linux users are still encountering a problem.

Added fallbacks to the custom pattern shaders so that if the shaders fail, the game is still playable and the vehicles will render with fallback shaders. The custom pattern and colors dialogue will not work however apart from changing ColorOne and ColorTwo.

Removed "reversed" field in launch protocol launching and landing properties.

Removed BETA dialog and top icon.
&lt;title&gt;Final Notes&lt;/title&gt;&lt;font&gt;Tiny&lt;/font&gt;
Please report any issues you find &lt;link&gt;https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/issues&lt;/link&gt;(here.) or on the discord server.
  </description>
  <!--Static parameterless method to execute when update log is executed-->
  <actionOnUpdate></actionOnUpdate>
  <!--Show update log on next startup.-->
  <update>false</update>
  <!--Testing mode prevents the update from saving over the UpdateLog file-->
  <testing>false</testing>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the right of the mod's name-->
  <rightIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Github</name>
      <icon>githubIcon</icon>
      <url>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <icon>discordIcon</icon>
      <url>https://discord.gg/zXDyfWQ</url>
    </li>
    <li>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <icon>steamIcon</icon>
      <url>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2356577528</url>
    </li>
  </rightIconBar>
  <!--Icon bar shown to the left of the mod's name-->
  <leftIconBar>
    <li>
      <name>Patreon</name>
      <icon>patreonIcon</icon>
      <url>https://www.patreon.com/smashphil</url>
    </li>
	<li>
	  <name>Cursed Crew</name>
	  <icon>cursedCrewIcon</icon>
	  <url>https://discord.gg/NNe2VxAU7Z</url>
	</li>
  </leftIconBar>
</UpdateLog>